{
    "subject": "resource/Acacio_Gabriel_Viegas",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Indian_medical_doctors",
    "human_readable": "Acacio Gabriel Viegas is a subject of Category: Indian medical doctors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835432767868042,
            "question": "Is Acacio Gabriel Viegas an Indian medical doctor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8234900236129761,
            "question": "To what category does Acacio Gabriel Viegas belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7634027600288391,
            "question": "What is Acacio Gabriel Viegas' profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6388941407203674,
            "question": "What nationality is Acacio Gabriel Viegas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5280697345733643,
            "question": "Can you name some Indian medical doctors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942173361778259,
            "question": "What field does Acacio Gabriel Viegas work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133702218532562,
            "question": "How does Acacio Gabriel Viegas contribute to society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40109214186668396,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by Indian medical doctors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27902209758758545,
            "question": "What is the role of medical doctors in healthcare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1585996448993683,
            "question": "What are the qualities of a good medical doctor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Acacio Gabriel Viegas is a subject of Category: Indian medical doctors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3542_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the role of medical doctors in healthcare?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3542_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by Indian medical doctors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3542_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Acacio Gabriel Viegas contribute to society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3542_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3542_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about Acacio Gabriel Viegas being an Indian physician, and his contributions to public health, including the detection of the bubonic plague in Bombay. The category \"Indian medical doctors\" seems to be a valid description for him based on the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Dr. Acacio Gabriel Viegas, describing his role as an Indian physician and his significant contributions to public health in India, particularly during the bubonic plague outbreak in Bombay. This aligns with the statement that he is a subject of the category \"Indian medical doctors.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}